Goddess Bast, time is running out.
Help me heal my brother.
And I won't doubt it
your existence again.
- His pulse dropped.
- The sequence is almost over.
- Grio, give me control.
- As you wish, Princess.
- What is the success rate?
- At 25%.
I have to try something else.
King Chala's heartbeat
decreased to 31 beats per minute.
- Princess, you must go next to him.
- I have to think. Get out.
Get out!
- What is the success rate?
- At 29.1%.
Print it!
I know it's urgent, but I have to
to warn you
This synthetic heart is nothing like it
to have the desired effect.
I do not care!
It should work.
- Gray...
- Yes, princess?
What is my brother's heart rate?
Your brother is with the ancestors.
No...
Thanks for the gift.
By King Anda Raja T'Challa.
Of the Black Panther.
His son Putra Raja T'Chaka.
My son.
Descendants of the great King Basenga,
Of the first Black Panther.
He left us and went away.
We honor the ancestors.
I'll miss you...
Sync / Render Dialogs: lykos478
GreekDiamond
Exclusive Presents
A YEAR LATER
UN, GENEVA, SWITZERLAND
It is an honor for me to invite
Your Majesty Queen Ramon,
Princess Lumumba,
and the Queen of Wakanda.
Sir, Secretary.
I want to speak for everyone
of the Member States when I say,
that I am deeply disappointed
since the failure of Wakanda
to live up to their promises,
to become a global player,
to overcome international challenges,
to share resources and collaborate
fully for vibranium.
France has said,
that vibranium
can be used
for weapons production
mass destruction.
The substance does not activate
the metal detectors.
This is a safety hazard
and the non-proliferation treaty.
I give the floor to Queen Ramon.
Our policy has always been not to
we ever deal with vibranium
under any circumstances.
Not because of potential
dangers of vibranium,
but at your own risk.
FOUR FAMILIES
WAKANDA ANSOGOU, MALI
The image on the monitor went black.
Calm down!
Fall to the floor!
Where is the vibranium?
Who has access to it?
Pretend to be polite.
But we know why you're talking
inside government buildings
and in military installations.
"The king is dead."
Black Panther is gone.
They lost their patron.
Now we have the opportunity to...
"...we attack."
- Varius, where is your spear?
- Suri gave me these.
I prefer them.
Our ancestors gave us the spears.
... on and off.
Nothing changes under my watch.
Yes, General.
I said don't take them.
Last night an installation of ours
was attacked.
I can prove that the UN
is behind it
as it downloads to your phone.
And as for the identity of the culprit...
Kneel down!
Here is.
Consider the answer to this
the attack as a friendly gesture.
Further attempts to steal our resources
will be considered an attack
and will cause
a stronger reaction from us.
We mourn our king.
But don't believe at all,
that Wakanda has lost the ability
to protect its resources.
We know your efforts
which are under development
to find vibranium
outside of Wakanda.
And I wish you good luck.
Atlantic ocean
Rotor 625 requested clearance to land.
See you inside.
- Didn't you retire?
- I thought so too.
The odds of finding vibranium
they should be very few.
I think so too.
Cabin pressure good.
240 meters.
- Move to the next layer.
- All systems OK.
Received.
We have reached the bottom.
Great then, Salazar, you're close.
This is awesome.
The drill seems to have
hit something like metal.
At least it's stable.
I've never seen a drill before
to be so shattered.
Amen, man.
Vibran in the ocean.
Let's get rid of the tracker.
It's all we have.
We are heading
in the vibranium detector.
- Everything went dark.
- Power supply stopped.
I'll take care of it from now on.
What the hell was that?
Jackson, did you see that too?
Salazar's beats.
Salazar, can you take a picture?
A jellyfish.
I have never seen such a color before.
Rescue Squad, alert.
Salazar, Jackson's Vital Organs
they do not work. You see him;
- No, he left.
- What do you mean, he left?
Salazar, can you hear me?
Salazar?
NO SIGNAL
Smith, something is wrong.
- What sound is that?
- Where is that sound coming from?
From the west, finally?
West, do you see anything?
- It's a sonic attack.
- Wear earplugs.
We are under attack.
Send in a strike team.
Help, help. 625 rotors here.
Send help immediately.
He's from Wakanda.
Of course.
Henderson!
We have to get out of here.
Come!
- What happens;
- Get down from there.
Chase her!
Throw, Throw, Throw!
Fly, get rid of them!
- They leave.
- Oh my god...
- Take us away.
- We are OK.
Where's the strike team?
The code is blue.
Everyone is dead.
- What happened;
- They're pulling us back!
Wait!
The Queen of Wakanda gave yesterday
a strong speech at the United Nations,
while the captured mercenaries
were brought before the Assembly.
The Queen is restored
as regent of Wakanda,
when King Chala died
last year from an unknown illness.
This small nation is preparing for battle
and is increasingly isolated.
Highness...
We are approaching the border.
We returned home.
- Princess...
- Wait a minute, I'm doing something.
- I know, but...
- You're interrupting my thoughts.
- Suri.
- Mother.
I wanted to tell you that the queen has arrived.
Thanks.
You make me nervous. One day the artificial
intelligence will kill us all.
Artificial intelligence
it's not like in the movies.
It's exactly what I tell him to do.
I wish all kids were like that.
Everyone seems to be working hard.
This is the emergency team.
There can be many threats
out there and we find the solutions.
- What is this;
- Uniforms for soldiers.
It provides the user with increased
strength, speed and endurance.
But like everything they don't like it.
- Which one;
- He hates them.
What about creating a heart?
Have you ever thought
that he would not approve?
sorry princess
Nakia, Princess of Yaa,
is trying to find you again.
- Maybe I should...
- Be careful with the calculations
and don't distract me.
As you wish princess.
We don't need the filter.
We need new technology.
What will happen to black panther?
This title has stuck with the nation for centuries.
Black Panther is a thing of the past.
I wasn't trying to save the title.
I was trying to save my brother.
Shuri...
- What day is today;
- Tuesday.
Date, son.
- My brother died.
- It was a year ago.
- Have you planned anything?
- Yes. We must be together.
- Now?
- Yes.
Just leave the chemotherapy pearls.
You won't need them where we're going.
Also the other two.
Sit here with me and alone.
It's the only way for them to heal
the wounds after T'Challa's death.
I'm fine, mother.
Do not worry about me.
He left, but I moved on.
Chala is dead,
but it doesn't mean it's gone.
When the disease killed
your brother
I had to lead a nation
wounded in a world in crisis.
But I still went to the bushes.
I wandered until I found water,
and then I sat down.
So I did the ritual
which I will show you now.
I found your brother in the breeze.
He pushed me gently but firmly,
whose hand was on my shoulder.
It's been a while,
but it was there.
He wasn't there, mother.
The presence you felt
it is an illusion of the mind
to entertain you
or to please you.
Only that.
What feeling do you feel?
when you think of your brother?
It brings you comfort...
...or sadness?
Come on, my child.
- Where did you find this;
- Does not matter;
What do they have to do with ritual?
We burn the funeral clothes to
end the mourning period
and start new relationships
leaving our loved ones.
I don't know, mom.
If I sit I will think
my brother for a long time...
... not the clothes I burned.
The whole world does that.
Shuri...
Suri, there's something you have to do
to tell you about your brother.
Mother, wait.
What are you doing;
- Is it part of the ceremony?
- No it is not.
Keep still!
Who are you and how did you get in here?
This place is perfect.
The air is still pristine.
And the water...
My mom told me about it.
protected country,
where people never leave
or change their lifestyle.
What reason did you have to reveal?
this secret in the world?
I don't like repeating myself.
Who you are;
I have many names.
My folks call me Kukulan.
My enemies call me Namor.
The US military found vibranium
under my own Royal rule.
I could stop the export,
but we needed
the help of wakanda,
so that it doesn't happen again.
They have a machine developed
by a scientist.
Vibranium is only found here.
Mom, he's covered in it.
Your son revealed
the power of vibranium, in the world.
It had caused other countries to terminate
this planet after that.
His choice put us in danger.
I think you can find some
researchers and bring them to me.
It's only natural that Wakanda should help
in solving our dilemma.
You are sneaking into my country
and you tell me what is fair.
My army is so
as numerous as blades of grass
and their power is incomparable.
I would not return under any other circumstances.
When you find the researchers, burn them.
Then I'll be there in no time.
For your own sake,
please don't say my name
to anyone outside of Wakanda.
Did you see the feathers on his ankles?
How did he do it?
We must convene the Council.
Heaven Scrapers has not
recorded activity.
Was the river border breached?
I wish my soldiers were there,
this fisherman would already be in front of you.
If your army was there,
they would still lie there dazed.
- You are a bald devil.
- Show each other respect.
Respect?
- These people should be ashamed.
- Watch how you speak, Jabari.
As I said, he didn't show up
on some surveillance camera.
- Not even on the radar.
- Did he swim 100 kilometers?
And he claims to lead a large army.
He wants us to catch an investigator
American to kill him?
Do it.
We never had an enemy that had vibranium
and we don't have Black Panther
to protect us.
Why did you let Kilman take the throne?
and burn all heart-shaped potions.
- Baku, what do you want us to do?
- Find the fisherman and kill him.
If we do what he asks now,
what will prevent him from coming
and demand more?
Sit down.
- Is it my idea or is it ugly?
- It's your idea.
It works;
Yes, the machine can
to detect vibranium
through water, rocks
and heavy metals.
Whoever did this
he is an excellent inventor.
Come and see.
Some pieces are manufactured
By order,
while others look like something out of a mantra.
I still find it hard to believe
that there is vibranium outside of Wukanda.
There may have been two meteorites.
The planet is covered mostly by water,
so of course the others
to end up there.
- This changes everything we know.
- The mountains, all the myths...
- They are etched in my mind.
- That sounds painful.
Then we have to find
this researcher.
I have an idea.
- I'll need the princess.
- Don't subject her to this.
- She's not ready at all.
- Your Highness...
It would do her good to get out a little.
Maybe he needs it.
And I can handle
blindfolded Americans.
They are not the ones that worry me.
He got past our defenses.
- It will not happen again.
- He's not alone.
He wants to be with me.
When are we going to visit?
my favorite colonist?
ALEXANDRIA
VIRGINIA
Come on...
Yes, I'm in.
I follow.
Slower.
- You couldn't call?
- I didn't know your number?
We are looking for the scientist
who discovered the vibranium detector.
Then you were in the Atlantic.
Ship drilling, many dead...
- What happened;
- Seriously?
It was us and the frogmen.
30 of the best
and two officers.
My personal friend, he died in one hit.
- They were looking for vibranium...
- Wakanda is not behind this.
Then who was it?
For this to work...
When I give you information,
you have to give me something too.
We can't tell you that.
We need to communicate
with the investigators before it is too late.
You owe me this, Ross.
You owe it to my brother.
Okay, listen.
An agent was sentenced to death
with less than I will tell you now.
And our new boss is like a hawk.
We have to be very careful.
You also need to be careful
and be quick.
USA needs new engines,
and the girl is the only one
to the world that can make it.
- And they will chase it.
- Girl?
CAMBRIDGE
MASSACHUSETTS
- You forgot to transfer money.
- Yes.
- It's 800, right?
- That was yesterday.
- Now it's interest.
- This is robbery.
I made my own robot arm.
I just fixed the algorithm.
And how much will it cost?
Thanks
- Is this an iPhone?
- Primitive.
Your Highness, we found the investigator...
00:35:59,130 ​​--&gt; 00:36:02,492
partner for Wakanda schools.
I hope he is a professor.
She is a student, a mother.
We can't give her to Namor.
Bring her to Wakanda.
Yes, Your Highness.
- I'm in charge now.
- Let me talk to her.
- It would be more subtle.
- I can be discreet.
- What is;
- Nothing.
- Is this makeup?
- Nice.
- Is the shadow wrong?
- No, Fendi. You look fine.
I can look like a student.
I can do it.
You have five minutes.
- Yes?
- Riri Williams?
I don't accept visitors.
You must visit
my website.
This is an encrypted file.
I'll leave it here.
Are you...
You are Princess Suri.
What are you doing here;
Will you recruit me?
No. I came for the scout
of the vibranium you made for the Co.
I didn't make it for the CIA,
but as a metallurgical mission.
- Homework;
- The teacher said it was impossible.
But we are young
talented and black.
Maybe we don't say that in Wakanda.
- How old are you;
- 19.
A genius is not recognized
always by the elders.
- How much will it take?
- Several months.
Several months?
The hardest part was
to find enough leaves.
Is Wakanda mad at me?
Not just us.
You're in danger here.
Pack your things and come with me.
I have calculus in a quarter of an hour...
Okay.
Okay, wait here.
I want to go to the bathroom.
- I had it under control.
- I said five minutes. Six passed.
Get out of my room.
Get out!
Don't come one step closer!
You see how they teach children
to deal with the guests?
- Do you have a spear with you?
- You brought a spear.
- I like.
- Put it down.
- You're going to get hurt.
- Leave me, my daughter.
Girl, I'm giving you two choices.
You can come to Wakanda
alive or unconscious.
You should take more care
your appearance, than your face.
- Do you find it funny?
- No it is not.
- I told you.
- You were fine.
Let's go.
Let's tell him to come
to fight alongside the mermaid
with ankle feathers,
who wants to kill him, alone.
You can do it easily.
You and your heater.
Here you go;
Where are we;
I built some cars for the boss.
And it allows me to work.
I have to get my laptop.
- Please don't touch anything.
- Do not worry.
It may not seem,
but it is my life's work.
Well, the image on the screen
do you have it on your laptop too?
And you've left it at that
open in the workshop?
It is encrypted at 2065-bytes.
Impressive.
- Have you ever been locked out?
- Yes, a whole semester.
I had to build a quantum computer
to crack my own encryption.
What technology is this?
- Is it Stark technology?
- I said don't touch anything.
Princess, the police just arrived.
- Who is this;
- My artificial intelligence.
They surround us.
You said a mermaid is chasing me.
These are Federalists.
I don't need this.
I swear.
This is not going to go very well.
I was very dumb.
The Princess of Wakanda has arrived
at my door, then all was lost.
I'm thinking of risking it, with the mermaid.
At least he hasn't
nothing to do with the FBI.
Namor sank a boat
of SIA because of your machine.
So for them it is the least
that you should worry about.
We have to work together to get out.
General, we are surrounded.
- Maybe we should split up.
- This is not possible.
- Do the vehicles work?
- No.
Everything works,
like these machines.
Forget it.
After all, there are three of us.
There are two of you.
I'll take this.
I knew the. Don't tell me
that you made it in two months?
It took me ages with this one.
- Have you ever thrown it away?
- It can fly;
There are many channels on YouTube
that guide you how to fly.
It's fantastic.
We have an arrest warrant
for Riri Williams!
We have a wireless device
so we will communicate.
General Okoi and Princess Shuri,
go out with your hands up.
- What scrap metal.
- Be careful with these.
The key is on the chair.
When we cross the bridge,
they won't be able to catch us.
We have to separate.
The laboratory is not our home.
- Then get in the car.
- He always has to shout.
We will break the door in three,
two one.
FBI!
Don't move.
- What was that;
- He has an Iron Man suit!
Stay still!
- So it flies.
- Gray...
- Yes, Princess.
- ...now!
Remote control activated.
Let's go!
Grio, turn on the video.
- Gray...
- Yes, General.
Take me to the princess.
Otherwise, I will nail
my spear to your editor
and you won't be able to edit
data for the next century.
Give me some time, General.
Okay, I'm coming to you.
- Grio, leave the control to me, now!
- I just opened the way for you.
You are in control General.
Manual control activated.
- We have to find a hiding place.
- Let's cross the river.
They have a block on the bridge.
Princess, you are being watched by a drone.
- At what height?
- Nine km.
Wait, I'll arrange it.
Think, a little Riri, because you have to solve
the equation that is equal to
with the relative speed.
Riri, you can't make it
the drone without an oxygen mask.
Oxygen level: 55%.
Eight and a half kilometers.
Oxygen level: 30%.
Maximum acceleration. Regulation
Euler's point of view and I arrived.
Oxygen level: 0%.
The drone is no longer following you.
Altitude:
At 500 km it drops.
Rin, are you okay?
Riri!
I am fine.
No.
I have a special tradition
in three, two, one...
Well done Riri!
What happened to him;
What happened; Shuri! Shuri!
The princess situation
is stable.
She will regain consciousness soon.
Take one more step
and I will kill you all.
Put your gun down!
Kill the scientist.
I will take the witnesses.
Understandable.
It's blue;
Kill the woman first.
You don't want to mess with Namor.
You are not worthy of my sword.
Why are you late?
We don't have time for bullshit.
Perfect!
- Wait!
- Enable translator.
I am Shuri, Princess of Wakanda.
Take me to Namor.
Don't bother the girl.
"Should we capture them alive?"
"Yes, Atuma."
"Inhale."
Shuri!
Ross, Co.
Witnesses;
No, but we think so
that they are Wakandans.
- Langley says they're coming.
- Who called you?
She.
- Director de Fontaine.
- Seriously?
They think they are Wakandans.
We monitor everything.
That's why I called you.
You look fine.
Are you done with the gym?
- Yes, last year.
- Then let me ride a bike.
I am the agent in charge.
Well done. Would you mind
tell me what happened here?
- Yes.
- Nice.
Okay, so what happened.
We thought it was a car accident,
but we could not find the car.
- Was it like this when you came?
- Yes.
We think someone took the car out
off the road and fell into the river.
You can't be serious.
To go to the laboratories immediately.
Send it to the NSA immediately.
Ross, would you mind?
take me back to langley?
- The trip is eight hours.
- We will talk about the case.
I actually want too
to apologize for some
things i said when we got married
They are blue and have superpowers.
They came out of the water above
on the backs of whales.
I killed three of them,
But they got up again.
I want to start right away
to search for the princess.
Okay.
You will be stripped of your position
leader of the Wakanda military
and your status as a warrior.
May I speak, Your Highness?
Yes, you can talk.
I beg you...
I have given everything.
Let me die to save
my country and my throne.
I am begging you.
- Let me make amends.
- Make amends?
I don't know if my daughter
is she alive or dead
Perhaps we are too hasty.
She raised her spear against
of her husband for the sake of Wakanda.
And where is her husband now?
A place he can go.
Mine is with the ancestors.
I am the queen of more
powerful nation in the world,
and i lost my whole family!
Didn't I give everything?
Get up, general.
I stood up for you when
killmonger took the throne.
But you and the board members
council together you supported him,
when I ran to Jabari for protection.
I warned you not to take it
my daughter on this mission,
and you lost her.
So today you are done.
Are you here, Grio?
Yes, my Queen.
Were you with Suri when she was kidnapped?
Yes I was.
You can spot
the chemotherapy pearls?
We found bullets all over Cambridge.
The people of Wakanda
he was indeed in town.
But how did they find out
who made the machine?
As these are extreme
confidential information.
Got a new ringtone?
- I have to answer, boss.
- Leave the formalities now. Answer it.
Hello my love.
I'm with my boss.
Yes now
- Which just left.
I will work from home
and then I'll take a shower.
- Everett Ross?
- Queen Ramonda?
What do you do with the chemical?
suri's pearl?
I didn't know it was hers.
I found them at the crime scene.
Do you have students at school?
Suri tried to save her,
but they have both been kidnapped.
Who was he kidnapped by?
SIA thinks it's you.
I'm afraid they'll find out how I drove
Shuri and Okoye in the right direction.
I want to help them, but
I need to know what's going on.
There is a new one
global power in the game.
The country we are watching or do you mean someone else?
I can't say much more now.
Please let me know if the govt
decide to act
based on her suspicions.
Will do it.
Listen, if there's anything I can do
to help, tell me.
I owe Suri my life.
Grio, is Suri wearing her earrings?
They were lost in the North Atlantic
but her captors spoke Yucatecan.
APPLICANT'S CAPITAL
"HAITI"
Welcome.
Do you want to speak to the manager?
There she goes.
Very good...
Good morning.
Excuse me for a moment.
Lady Queen Mother...
Everything here is a lesson for children.
They paint the walls, feed and care
the fish do whatever it takes.
Some of my concepts are familiar
but you use
different material now.
Yes, we use what we can
to find here in Haiti.
We missed you at Tsala's funeral.
- Queen mother...
- It's been six years since you left.
I thought you would attend
at least at the ceremony.
I was afraid, like the funeral
would put a definitive end to it.
Nakia, daughter of Yaa.
You will always be her daughter
Wakanda wherever you go.
You know death is not the end.
Thanks
How is everyone at home?
- Suri was kidnapped.
- How why?
You have infiltrated many countries before.
It has been a long time.
I was a different person then.
I need someone who can find her
and save her without being seen.
Who would dare
challenge Wakanda?
- Oh my god.
- Breathe.
Don't ask me to breathe.
Where the hell are we?
- I am not sure.
- Oh my god, what is this?
Their larvae emit light.
Just calm down.
There is no new black panther
where can you call
No. It doesn't work that way anymore.
Black Panther is in the past.
Now that we've been kidnapped,
is there no black panther?
Princess.
The members of the royal family
here they wear traditional clothes.
Do you understand what he says;
- They made it for me.
- This is so bad.
It's in every movie.
Princess Leia,
Belle from "Beauty and the Beast"
the white girl from "Indiana Jones".
You will be surprised to see what you need
to wear to the Warriors' Feast.
Come with me.
- You won't leave me here, will you?
- I'll be back.
I'll be back. Calm down.
Do you want to eat;
YUCATAN, MEXICO
- Good evening lady.
- How can I help you;
My name is Maria Aldana.
I am a student of Merida.
I do not care.
Go away please
Yes of course. I don't want you
offend...give me a moment.
My teacher mentioned a survey
to which you replied that you have met...
... an inconceivable man.
No one wants to talk to strangers.
- I'm begging you.
- Disappear.
I met him too.
Sometimes I saw a winged man
in the beach.
We thought it was a soul
of Kukulkan, the winged one
snake god,
which rules in him
the world and the under...
I want to go to this beach.
I warn you.
Kukulkan was there a lot
before you and me
Others sought him and brought him
in their hearts bad faith
and they never came back.
They disappeared into the depths
forever.
Princess.
Welcome.
Please come closer.
- This is beautiful.
- It belonged to my mother.
All artifacts
is from Central America,
mainly of the 16th century.
Have you lived since then?
Your mother was human
It was, but something else happened.
- How?
the important
it's not the how but the why.
ZAMA,
YUCATAN
My mother's people
were evicted from their farms
because of the Spanish invaders
who brought smallpox with them.
Hate for the language
and doctrine from another world.
They had to face starvation,
war and disease
My folks turned to Chuck...
... the God of rain and wealth.
Chuck showed us the way
of our spirit,
how he could save his people.
Chuck gave them a plant that
grows on a blue stone
My mother was pregnant
to me at the time
and he did not dare to eat
from the plant so as not to lose me.
No, I'm pregnant.
But the spiritual was reassuring.
Your child is sick.
This might save him.
Your child will be
the first born in our new home.
Think of this gift as a promise
that he will be our new king
Everyone got sick.
Thus their life and existence ended there.
The plant took away their ability
to breathe the oxygen of the land.
But he allowed them to breathe
in the sea.
They settled in the ocean
away from wars and diseases.
Come on!
That's where my mother gave birth to me...
...and I became the first man
who was born in Talokan.
The plant gave me winged ankles
and ears pointing to the sky.
I was a mutant.
I was flying in the sky.
But my age has slowed.
And I could breathe
the air of my ancestors.
My mother was getting old
and mourned the life he knew
and died heartbroken.
She made me promise her
that I would bury her in her homeland.
But I wasn't ready
for what I would see there.
Whose son is this?
Get ready!
You are the devil
Satan's seed.
A Spanish priest cursed me
as she was dying in my arms.
He called me...
"The Loveless Child".
"Child without love"..
And from his words I got my name
"Namor".
Because I had no love
for the world of earth.
Why are you telling me all this?
To understand why you should
to kill the researcher.
What if we take her to Wakanda?
Let us go. I give you my word
that the girl will stay in my hometown.
- I can't risk it.
- Then hold me.
I would like to see your nation.
You can't go like that.
Your body will go into immediate shock.
Your blood will be poisoned
and the water pressure will break
every bone in your body,
or you can wear a suit.
We have many options.
Stay close to me.
Namor, wait!
TALOCAN CAPITAL
Hello.
It is very beautiful.
It is made of vibranium.
Yes, to the depths of the ocean I brought
the sun to my people.
I know you want me not to kill
the scientist
But now you see
what should i protect
Your hunch was right, Nakia
I spotted Suri's earrings.
The signal originates
from an underwater cave
in depth approx
140 meters from the surface.
Queen, I found her trail.
It comes from an underwater cave.
If it's down there, I'm sure
that I will meet resistance.
How do you want me to act?
Take back the princess
by any means possible.
I'll try to pull Namor out.
You are the first person from
surface that came to Talocan.
Please accept this
as a token of my gratitude.
It is made from the plant
who saved Talocan.
You are young, Princess.
If you get old like me...
You understand that we all lose
everyone we love
But when I lost my brother,
the feeling was different.
He suffered in silence.
And when he finally asked me for help,
I couldn't give it to him.
How does that make sense?
My ancestors gave
gifts and skills...
to help save
my brother and I couldn't.
Why;
I don't have an answer to this question.
As my ancestors used to say:
"Only the most broken people
they can become great leaders"
I admire what you have done here
and how you protect
your people?
But as the princess of Wakanda,
I can't let you kill her.
My nation will not rest
until I come back.
I'm not leaving without her.
We need to settle this peacefully.
The issue is no longer about the scientist.
For centuries nations have conquered
and enslave people like us
only for our resources.
Since the day I buried my mother,
I prepare my people
for the time they will come to invade
And this instrument
it's a sign that the time has come.
I need to know if Wakanda
is he an ally or an enemy..
There is no middle ground.
So you plan to start
war all over the world...
and you want wakanda to help you?
This is madness.
No nation would plunder
Wakanda if given the chance.
If we ally, we will protect
each other from the attacks.
Once they stop threatening us,
then we will eliminate them.
The scientist
will return to Wakanda.
And what if Wakanda refuses?
The researcher will die...
And Wakanda will be
the first nation to fall.
- Are you going to attack my country?
- Yes.
Listen to me. Wakanda will not win
never a war against the Talokan.
He wants to offer you something,
the Kukulkan.
I heard you that night you were
with your mother near the river.
You said you wanted to burn the world down.
Let's burn him together.
CO
LANGLEY VIRGINIA.
Queen Raimonda refuses
to sell us vibranium.
And now they kidnapped the young woman
who made the machine.
Sincerely, Riri Williams
he is a genius with good performance.
Wakanda recruited her.
With the program they created.
But you sent an army at night.
To arrest
the princess of a superpower.
The president,
he wants to attack Wakanda.
- What kind of aggressive action?
- Destabilization.
Special Officer Ross
is the expert.
What do you think, Ross?
My sources tell me
that something else is involved.
- Another nation?
- I do not know maybe.
You have to give me
enough time to investigate it.
Otherwise, we will meet
at war against a country,
which we cannot even comprehend
military capabilities.
- Ms. Director?
- He's an expert.
I think the attack
in Wanda it would be wrong.
- You are welcome;
- We have a problem..
KURAL BELCHO
KIP VERDE
Is my daughter alive?
The princess is well and alive.
He asked to be transferred to Talocan
and it will remain there for a while.
01:22:14,605 ​​--&gt; 01:22:18,566
What can I give you in exchange?
- There is nothing.
- I have a different opinion
Americans think
in charge of Wakanda
for the attack on the research ship.
Give me back my daughter
and the researcher
otherwise I will tell them about you.
If you tell the Americans about us,
Or try to find us,
or see even a single ship
of Wakanda in the ocean...
i will kill the princess...
and then I will come to Wakanda
and i will kill you
So what happened?
She wants to declare war on her world
surface. He asked me to help him.
We have to think.
We will never leave here.
- Throw your spear!
- Kill the princess!
Throw away your knife.
You
I'll kill you.
Let her go
and I won't kill you.
Suri, wave your hand.
Are you ok;
Give me your beads!
I can save her.
Suri, I don't know who she is,
but we must hear what he has to say.
Look, I hit her with a sonic.
it is lethal from this distance.
he will not be able to survive.
You do not understand.
This will lead to war.
- Have you knocked?
- No.
Thanks.
You are welcome.
Griot, take us to Wakanda.
What happened my daughter?
Here come the Wakandans,
and they took her.
Kukulkan...
... can you save me?
Passed away;
Yes.
Rest in Peace.
They came...
while you were talking to the queen?
She was not to be trusted.
The princess saw our house.
What will stop them?
to attack the Taloscans?
I will stop them.
Rise up, Taloscans!
Arm yourself, Taloscans!
It blinded me...
the hope...
of the alliance.
Me too...
I put us in danger...
all of you.
The Taloscan...
It won't change...
his place, once again.
Namora.
Let's go.
When we're done with them...
they will never think...
again to approach
the Taloscan.
Arm yourself, Taloscans!
We're glad you're back, princess.
The town has been tense since you left.
Reinforce sound barriers
in all directions.
- Princess?
- Neka.
Thank the ancestors.
I just wanted to give you these.
No, keep them.
They may be needed soon.
Is that where you got it from?
It is true that you saw down
from the waters an empire?
Yes.
It's very nice,
but they are dangerous, Anika.
So Miss Riri Williams?
What do you think of 'Wakanda'?
The stories don't do this place justice.
It's great here,
but I really want to go home.
- Be patient.
- Can I take my mother?
The Princess was saved by Nakia.
Glory to Hanuman.
The spy saved Wakanda, again.
The queen probably
he will reward her with exile.
Okoye, welcome.
Thank you my sister.
After the attack of Thanos,
you left without saying anything
It hurt me.
I'm sorry I wasn't there with you.
It wasn't easy for me.
He was the King
and Black Panther, for everyone.
But for me...
... was everything.
My T'Chala.
When he was taken from me so suddenly.
I had to get away.
and pick up my pieces.
I couldn't go on with my life
as if nothing had happened.
We are under attack.
Keep it.
Let's help them!
Are you ok;
Griot, activate defense.
- Suri, where are you?
- To the lab, I'm coming.
Stay where you are, it's an order!
I'm with Anika, mom. We can
to provide air support.
Anika, don't let her go
to leave the laboratory.
Mom, I can't hear you.
You're on vacation. See you later.
- Did you hang up on the Queen?
- I hung up on my mother.
There is a difference.
Come on, lets go.
Invaders!
Mum! Mum!
Turn back!
Paramedics submit
in sound hypnosis.
Take the child!
- Close your ears, General.
- Yes, that's what I do.
- Can I help;
- Come here quickly.
Warrior!
Cross your arms, kid.
Nakia.
We're going to find your mom, okay?
The fisherman!
We dropped the Palace defenses.
The rest is up to you.
Aid!
- He is very fast.
- And faster in the water.
- System Bypass.
- I'm not going to leave you.
- You see him;
- Yes, there it is.
Go away, my daughter.
- What if I leave you?
- Run!
Let's go now!
Help the girl.
This happened because of her.
I'll be back in a week
with all my army.
Join us to fight.
Or I'll wipe out Wakanda
from the face of the earth.
Come my queen!
Mother.
Hold her back!
Bury your dead.
And mourn those you lost.
You are the queen now.
Let me! Mum!
Mum!
Wake up my queen.
Let me try.
Help her!
Mum.
Wake up!
Passed away.
Condolences from the country
of Jabari for your loss.
You must mourn accordingly
with ancestral rites.
- Don't bother with the techniques.
- Why are you here;
I promised your brother that I would
I would give you advice and protect you.
But now I need it
your advice today.
The elders of your tribe
they came to me with a proposal.
They want to evacuate the city
and set up camp at Jabari.
And now you want him to listen
the opinion of a little girl.
To mock tradition?
The world...
The world has deprived you of much.
You can no longer be considered a little girl.
It is in the interest of my people
to know which option you prefer.
The elders are desperate.
The city is vulnerable.
If you help them,
they will owe you a lot.
And what does your heart say?
Where does it close?
I just buried the last one
person who knew me well.
My heart is buried with her.
The oil is about to spoil.
- What are you doing here;
- I am hungry. And...
A tragedy struck the international community.
Sources can confirm,
the death of Queen Raimonda,
Lumumba's daughter.
The Western Allies blame...
civil strife...
as a possible cause of death...
So, do you have any comments?
I wonder what else
your friends are hiding from you.
What are you talking about;
I don't have any unauthorized ones
contact with the kingdom of Wakanda'
What about beads?
- Here you go;
- The beads?
There is an interception
before you deny anything.
I am aware of every conversation...
that you had between and the call,
that you committed treason with the queen.
May he rest in peace.
But that's good, good for us.
The Wakandans saved my life.
They are good people.
Have you thought about what they could do?
Have you thought about what we do?
If the United States were alone
country in the world with vibranium?
I have actually dreamed of this.
- Put, please...
- Director de Fontaine.
Your mother protected me
as if I were her child.
It's the least I can do
to try to return the favor.
- We need to weaken him.
- Even if it weakens...
the problem remains.
Black Panther ever
he didn't let Wakanda down.
Didn't you say Black Panther left?
My brother is dead.
But that doesn't mean
that the Black Panther is gone.
Griot, start benchmarking.
to make an artificial parasite
to put it in the fibers of the bracelet.
Yes, Princess.
Since these were cultivated
in vibranium-rich soil.
There may be similarities between
that we can take advantage of.
As you wish Princess.
- Upload my brother's DNA too.
- Uploading it now.
Why don't they look alike?
The physiology is completely different.
None of them fly either
she has pointy ears like him.
The women who guarded us
they put water in their mouths and throats.
That's what they did.
There are many organizations
which do not need gills
to extract oxygen
from the water, so...
For example the jellyfish.
Absorbs oxygen through the skin.
This process is called diffusion.
Every day that goes by without us choosing
some area is a wasted day.
We have to deal with Namor
before bringing his warriors here.
How do you treat a person?
who has so much power?
In the attack before the plane was shot down,
went back into the water.
Maybe he can draw power from her?
It breathes air and absorbs
oxygen from water.
If we find a way to keep him
dry will not be strong.
This is.
Grio, we have to move
the battle in a steam room.
- This happens;
- Yes, it is possible.
You will help us trap him.
Please show the missus
Williams her workplace.
Please come from here.
How old were you when you did?
your first machine?
Three years old.
My stepfather was a car mechanic
and he wanted to build airplanes.
He gave me tools
and let me work.
- Who taught you?
- My big brother.
I was the tip of the spear
of the Wakanda military.
This doesn't suit me at all.
Besides, I'm a citizen now.
I surrendered my gun.
I also made you a new spear.
- New;
- Yes.
- And what did you call this thing?
- The Midnight Angel.
- The Midnight Angel?
- Listen to me, Okoya.
It has potential. Sister,
You must be ready when I call you.
I am begging you.
- Suri.
- Yes?
How many of these did you make?
I was looking for you in Jabari barracks.
- I won't leave my house.
- You have a revolutionary spirit.
- Why did you join the warriors?
- Why are you interested;
I still have the desire to fight.
Tell me, Anika, daughter of Kiana,
do you still have the will to fight?
What do you have in mind;
Grio, what's the success rate?
98.7%, Princess.
Would you like me to print?
the heart shaped herb?
Hello, Suri.
I thought you were going back to Haiti.
I'm still Wakandan.
So that's what you're working on.
Yes.
What do you have here now?
It's an opportunity for Wakanda to have
back her patron.
This will be the greatest gift
and from the discovery of Basinga.
We'll find out soon enough.
Come.
- Gray?
- Yes, Princess.
Print it out.
- How will we know if it worked or not?
- It will shine!
You did it!
Let's not light incense
about the ancestors?
Only the Goddess Bast knows how they got there
the ancestors in this workshop.
- Surely I won't bury you?
- Yes.
I want you to be able to reach
in my chest if I have a seizure.
Failure;
He's kidding, right?
So;
Allow me to leave this
the heart-shaped herb
to give you
the power of the Black Panther
and take you to the Realm of the Ancestors.
Raimonda
please come to your daughter.
Mother;
- Ticks?
- Cousin;
How;
The important thing is not
the how but the why, right?
- You chose me.
- No, I didn't.
I would never choose you.
- Why did you take the herb?
- To see my family.
No, that's nonsense.
You didn't think that the Ancestral Kingdom
it would be real, right?
- No.
- Then why did you take it?
You don't have to lie to me.
- To become strong.
- Get stronger why?
You see; We look alike
more than you think.
You took it to get revenge
the ancestors.
I'm not like you.
You got it for yourself.
You consume the potion and burn the rest.
Then you destroyed what was left.
An unworthy king
who is afraid of being replaced.
A coward.
I had the courage to do what was necessary
to change Wakanda.
How many people have I protected from you?
in Wakanda before I ascended the throne.
Panthers were cowards before me
and before T'Challa.
Don't mention my brother.
He's dead because of you.
Burn the herb,
leaving us vulnerable.
Namor came and killed my mother.
You are responsible for her death.
Do not blame me.
And don't underestimate your mother.
She sacrificed her life to protect
a young woman from the lost tribe.
Your father was a hypocrite.
He would have killed the girl.
He killed his own brother.
T'Challa was noble.
You let his killer live.
And you are here standing.
Will you be as noble as your brother?
Or you will do the right thing...
...like me;
Are you ok;
01:56:22,603 ​​--&gt; 01:56:24,389
Who did you see?
Nobody.
- What happens;
- I failed. Did not work.
Shuri...
- They abandoned me.
- They would never do that.
I did everything I had to do.
I remade the herb.
- Okay.
- I just did the stupid ritual
and what did i get?
- Why didn't they come?
- Just calm down.
Damn it...
Can I have it too?
I think so...
...that you will need a uniform.
- Many people come from the city.
- We need more space.
You are visitors. It is incredible
what you can achieve with anything.
The princess!
It succeeded!
Long live the Black Panther!
Namor believes
that Wakanda is weak.
He murdered our Queen...
...And destroyed the capital.
He thinks we are vulnerable.
...but now it is
time to attack
How; We don't even know
how to find him?
- We will bring Namor to us.
- Here again?
No, in a remote location.
Well.
Let's say it succeeds.
Who can fly and can
to be as strong as the Hulk.
...the right thing is to kill him?
We call for his death, when
his only crime was bullying.
What has changed, Lord Embaco?
His soldiers
they didn't call him General or King,
he was called Ku-kul-kan.
- What it means;
- "Winged Serpent Deity".
He believes that because we live in the mountains,
can't we read, books?
Elders, with your permission.
Would like to talk
with Lord M'Baku in private.
Okay.
Namor isn't done yet.
He promised to destroy
the surface world.
Now is our chance
to defeat him.
- What are you afraid of;
- The war.
If they see Namor
truly as God...
if we kill him,
we are in danger of perpetual war.
So what; Life wasn't worth living
my mother's perpetual war?
It's definitely worth it.
But that's not it
that he would like for you.
And that's not what I want...
...for my people.
You're talking about my mother
as if he is still with us.
You talk about what she would want for me.
For hopes and dreams...
but she is dead.
Passed away!
Namor choked her in front of me.
So her dreams, her goals,
and her hopes...
...they don't exist.
It doesn't matter anymore.
What matters is what I want,
and what I want is Namor dead.
And you will help me defeat him.
Understood?
We are leaving tomorrow morning.
- Good morning.
If we survive this,
Know you have one
home with me in Haiti.
hold my hand
Breathe.
Suri, be honest with me.
Who did you see when you took the herb?
If you go to war for revenge, you won't
fill the void you feel from the loss.
It will only grow
and it will consume you.
He already has.
Ku-kul-kan, a new machine
detects for vibranium in the ocean.
Where;
ATLANTIC OCEAN
Get out of the water!
For the Queen.
riri how are you
- Griot, can you send help?
- You finally asked me.
Come on, he's fast.
But I'm faster.
I got you.
It's up to you, Suri!
- Princess.
- No.
I am the Black Panther
and I came to take revenge.
The cells were activated.
What happened to you;
Would you like a glass of water?
- We have it!
- Namor has been arrested.
We're coming back.
Back to Wakanda!
We're leaving!
- What happens;
- They destroyed the sonic cannon..
This is not a good sign.
The ship lost its energy
and we have significant losses.
- Okay!
- Panther.
The virus!
The time has come.
For Wakanda!
- Griot, damage report.
- Destructive.
His spear is crafted
from crude vibranium.
- The ship will explode.
- Take us to the desert.
No!
Sink the ship!
I'm holding you, sister.
Warrior!
You speak the mother tongue.
You can use it
to greet your ancestors.
Get off me!
Well, come here.
You will pay tribute
to your ancestors.
Our ancestors will save us
if the princess doesn't hurry.
We might go find them.
Then let us take with us as many as we can.
It could have been different.
I need water.
Will you be noble like your brother?
Or will you do what needs to be done...
...like me;
I'm not like my brother
Namor will beg for mercy...
while I will be by his side
and I will watch him die.
King of the Empire
Wakanda Forever!
Suri.
Mother...
Show him who you are.
Surrender,
and Wakanda will protect
your seas and your secret.
Surrender,
and your people will live.
We were thirsty for revenge.
We will not allow it to be conquered.
Ι surrender.
Tulscans!
Let's go home.
Our battle is over here.
Wakanda Forever!
Thank you my love.
- Ready to go home?
- Only the police are waiting for me.
Do not worry.
But I won't help you with your lessons.
If you get caught, I can't help you.
- Did they say you wanted to talk to me?
- Yes.
Your outfit. It has a nice design, though
I can't let you take her.
Correctly. I think it is the least
that I could do.
I want to show you one last thing.
It took me a while to find
all the pieces in the river but it was worth it.
How...;
It's my father's car.
We were working on it before he died.
- Are you sure;
- Yes, I will send you to Boston.
and it will be there before you arrive.
Come here.
Panther, the transporter
for Miss Williams, arrived.
Take care of yourself.
Are you sure you won't come?
to see the Bulls in Chicago?
Sounds nice, but
I have something to take care of.
Now I present to you
Princess Suri.
The Black Panther!
Black Panther sends greetings...
But he won't be with us today...
I Em' Baku,
Chieftain of the Jabari clan
and son of Wakanda...
I would like to participate
in the challenge for the throne...
What's going on, son?
All my life I wanted
to fight with you
but I think you have submitted
to the Wakandans.
Black Panther had a lot
good reason to kill me...
Why do you think he didn't?
The Black Panther
he is the strongest man
to the most powerful nation on the surface
But he has no allies.
And now he has the sympathy
from the people of Talocan.
With this alliance...
The Talokan will be stronger than ever.
the surface world
will attack Wakanda
and Wakanda
will ask for our help.
Trust me!
- What the hell is this;
- Can't we go back?
- I do not know man. We'll lose an hour.
- Go see.
I will save us.
A tree blocks the road.
What do you want me to do;
I like you in chains.
When have I never seen you like this?
- Very funny.
- Get out!
Thanks.
- Thanks.
- You are welcome.
- Hello.
- Good morning.
Welcome!
I am glad to see you.
Everything is ready.
Just give me a moment.
In fact, I think everything should
to do it myself
Of course.
CAUTION CONTINUES
AND AFTER THE END TITLES
GreekDiamond
Exclusive Presents
Sync / Render Dialogs: lykos478
BLACK PANTHER
WAKANTA FOREVER
Shuri...
Can we sit with you?
This is my son, Toussaint.
Toussaint, this is your aunt, Suri.
Hello.
We had said it would be better
to grow up here.
Away from the pressure of the throne.
Your father, he prepared us
for his death, right?
But he didn't want us to come to the funeral.
He felt the time was not right.
So we did
our own ceremony for him.
- Did my mom meet him?
- Of course he met him.
- Nice to meet you.
- Also.
Toussaint is a nice name.
It has a rich history.
Thanks.
You are very good too. I think so;
My mom said you're good
in keeping secrets. Is true;
Yes, I can keep a secret.
Toussaint is my name in Haitian.
Who you are;
I am Prince T'Challa,
son of King T'Challa.
DEDICATED TO FRIEND BOBCAT